《黑镜》
血压和血氧饱和度怎么样
How are the pressures and saturation?
血压稳定 血氧饱和度100%
Pressures are good. Oxygen saturation is 100%.
- 有什么感觉吗 - 没有
- Feel anything? - No.
现在呢
How about now?
他这样做呢
And when he does that?
没感觉
Nothing.
好 都准备好了
OK. All set, then.
切第一道切口 给我高频电刀
Making initial incision. Hand me the Bovie.
已进入腹膜
We've entered the peritoneum.
真不敢相信我竟然没法自己生
I can't believe I couldn't do it.
我再也推不动了
I couldn't push anymore.
别说傻话了 用不着道歉
Don't be ridiculous. Don't apologize.
膀胱已拨开 切子宫切口
We've moved the bladder. Here's the uterine incision.
- 天啊 - 没事的
- Oh, God… - Hey, it's gonna be fine.
抓住我的手吧 我不会告诉别人的
I won't tell anybody if you want to hold my hand.
好了 准备好了 生命体征如何
OK, we're ready now. How are the vitals?
很稳定 你现在会觉得有点压力
Still good. You're gonna feel a little pressure now.
能看见后脑勺了
Occiput is visible and…
胎儿出来了
baby is out.
剪脐带
Cutting the umbilical cord.
她没事吧
Is she OK?
怎么了
What is it?
怎么…
What's…
- 她没事吧 - 没事的
- Say she's OK. - It's OK.
天啊 天啊
Oh, God! Oh, God…
- 她没事吧 - 放松 等一等 好吗
- Is she OK? - Just relax. Hold on. OK?
好样的
Good job.
她很健康
She's great.
她好漂亮
She's beautiful.
数三下 你张大嘴吃下去 好不好
One, two, three and open your mouth and eat this down, OK?
一 二 三 吃
One, two, three, boo.
不 嘴张得大大的 叉子才进得去
No, no. Big "Ah" and in it goes.
要这样吗 士兵
So, that's how it's gonna be, huh, soldier?
我不是士兵
I'm not a soldier.
换我来吧
You want me to take over?
你妈妈现在应该知道
I think your mother should know by now that.
外公我可不会轻言放弃
your grandfather's not a quitter.
一二三
One, two, three, and…
我想带萨拉去公园 你去吗
I want to take Sara to the park. You want to come?
不 不介意的话我就不去了
No, I'm gonna pass if you don't mind.
我想继续画画 把它画完
I'd like to get at that painting, get it finished.
- 那匹马吗 - 对
- The horse? - Yeah.
嗯 玩得开心
Yep. Have a good time.
不不
No, no.
妈妈
Mommy.
到喽
Here we are!
玛丽
Marie?
我就觉得是你
I thought it was you.
他叫米奇
This is Mikey.
- 你好 小家伙 - 是啊
- Hello, little guy. - Yeah.
你好呀
Hey, there.
- 他多大了 - 七个月
- How old is he? - He's seven months.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢
- Congratulations. - Yeah. Thank you.
猫咪
Kitty!
- 我好累 - 是啊
- I'm so tired. - Yeah.
希望有朝一日他能一觉到天亮
Hopefully he'll sleep through the night one of these days.
是啊 你已经熬过那个阶段了 萨拉多大了
Yeah, well, you're past that. How old's Sara now?
三岁了 她…
Sara is three and she's…
萨拉
Sara!
过来跟小弟弟打个招呼
Come say hi to this little boy.
萨拉
Sara?
- 萨拉 - 萨拉
- Sara! - Sara!
萨拉
Sara!
- 妈妈在找你 - 萨拉
- Mommy's looking for you! - Sara!
萨拉
Sara!
- 别急 我们会找到她的 - 别说了
- It's OK. We're gonna find her. - Stop!
- 女士 - 萨拉
- Lady! - Sara!
我找到她了
I found her!
她在小路那边 滚下山坡了
She was down by the track. Fallen down the slope.
她说她刚才在追猫
Said she… she followed a cat?
- 她去追猫了 - 真对不起
- She followed a cat. - I'm so sorry.
真对不起 对不起 妈妈在呢
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm right here.
天啊 对不起 对不起
Oh, God, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
《天使方舟》
- 萨姆布瑞尔女士 - 是我
- Miss Sambrell? - Yes.
萨拉 对吗 跟我来
And Sara, right? Follow me.
有人推荐你
You have a recommendation,
所以萨拉会参加我们的实验阶段
so Sara will be part of our trial period.
- 经过检测了吧 - 当然
- Well, it's been tested though, right? - Of course.
- 她不会做小白鼠吧 - 不会的
- I mean, she's not, like, a guinea pig. - Yes.
已经全面检测过了 百分百安全
It's all fully tested, perfectly safe.
只不过全面推广前 我们想精确调整
This is just us fine-tuning our subscription model.
订购模式
before the full launch.
看看这些孩子
Look at the kids.
我们想得到反馈
We're getting feedback on.
现实生活中哪种功能顾客用得最频繁
which features our customers use most in the real world.
你想上去吗 来吧
Do you wanna go up? Yeah!
目前得到的反馈非常好
Response so far is just incredible.
安全放心
The sense of security, peace of mind.
我们听到的使用经历非常让人振奋
I mean, the stories we've been hearing, they're inspirational.
你能看见屏幕吗
Can you see the screen?
- 那好吧 - 好了
- OK, then. - There you go.
- 你喜欢动画片吗 - 喜欢
- You like cartoons? - Yeah.
喜欢《愿望精灵小姐妹》吗
Yeah? Shimmer and Shine?
好
OK.
那你看吧 我马上回来 好不好
Then you watch that and I won't be a moment. OK?
- 这就完成了 - 是啊
- That's it? - That's it.
那么…
So…
我帮你设置好
Let's get you all set up.
- 我从头到尾教你一遍 好吗 - 好
- I'll run you through everything. OK? - OK.
有问题随时问
Feel free to ask any questions.
这是你的父母控制中心
This is your parental hub.
我把它和萨拉的植入物配对
I'm just pairing it with Sara's implant.
好了 设置好了
OK. We're all set.
这是萨拉当前的位置
So, this is Sara's current location,
当然 就是这里
which is here, of course.
看看
Oh, look at that.
要是她走丢了 你只需按这里
Now, if she ever goes missing, all you have to do is tap here,
输入密码 它就会自动通知执法部门
enter your PIN, and law enforcement is automatically notified.
好
OK.
这是她的生命体征
These are her vitals.
心跳很健康 她稍微有点缺铁
Healthy heartbeat. Oh, I see her iron levels are a little low.
她饭吃得怎么样
How is she eating?
她挑食得很 不爱吃绿色蔬菜 所以
Man, she's picky. Um, she hates greens, so…
给她吃点营养补充剂吧
You might want to think about nutritional supplements.
好
OK.
按这个图标
Now, tap this icon here…
转播她的视觉信号
to relay her optic feed.
这就是她现在看到的
This is what she's seeing now?
没错
That's right.
真是太厉害了
That's amazing.
妈妈 真好玩
Mommy! It's funny.
还有家长控制功能
And there are parental controls you can apply to that.
- 控制 - 限制内容
- Uh, controls? - Content limitations.
要是她看见了
If she witnesses something.
让她皮质醇水平上升的东西 比如压力
that causes her cortisol levels to rise, like stress,
它能覆盖住触发不利情绪的东西
it can kind of paint out whatever's triggering it.
- 我演示给你看 - 好
- Let me show you. - OK.
没事的 看
It's OK. Look.
看 这情景使得她皮质醇飙升 这是
See, the imagery causes a cortisol spike, and this…
过滤开
Filter on.
她现在的所见所闻
…is what she sees and hears.
好吧
OK.
我不确定我们会…
Yeah, I'm not sure that we'll…
都是可选操作
It's all optional.
好
Ok.
多少钱
How much?
不要钱 免费试用
Nothing. It's a free trial.
免费的
Oh, free.
- 好吧 - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
而且绝对安全
And it's completely safe.
我相信 宝贝
I'm sure it is, honey.
我已经两千岁了
I am 2, 000 years old…
我记得以前 我们会敞开大门
and I remember when we used to open up the door.
孩子爱怎样就怎样
and just let the kids be.
我记得因为你不装安全门栏
And I remember breaking my arm.
我摔断了胳膊
because you wouldn't get a baby gate.
那你的胳膊现在如何
And how is the arm now?
还可以
Feels OK.
你在吗 妈妈
Are you there? Mommy!
你在哪
Where are you?
妈妈
Mommy?
你在这儿吗
Are you here?
妈妈
Mommy?
- 怎么了 宝贝 - 我在找妈妈
- What's up, sweetheart? - I'm looking for Mommy.
你在找妈妈 我不知道她在哪
You're looking for Mommy? I got no idea where she's at.
楼上 去吧 去楼上找找
Upstairs. Go on. Go look upstairs.
妈妈 你在哪
Mommy, where are you?
妈妈 我听见你了
Mommy, I hear you.
我会找到你的
I'm gonna find you.
我听见你了 妈妈
I hear you, Mommy.
过滤开
Filter on.
你们会好好的吧
You guys gonna be all right?
我都把你安全养大了 你这不好好的吗
I raised you all right. You turned out OK.
是花了点时间 但你顺利长大了
Took you a while, but you did.
好了宝贝 待会见
All right, sweetheart. I'll see you later.
好好吓吓你外公 他应付得来
Terrorize your grandpa. He can handle it.
再见
Bye.
橙色吸管
Orange straw.
（威勒理疗诊所）
- 使劲推我的手 - 好
- OK, just push on my hand. OK. - Yeah.
放松
Relax.
再来 你就这么大劲吗
Again. Is that all you got?
你有好转
I think the range is getting better.
我还要多久才能继续骑摩托车
So how long till I can get back on the bike again, you think?
两周吧 但别骑太快
I'd say two weeks and maybe don't drive so fast.
好吧
Yeah, right.
好了 那么下周同一时间见
OK. So, same time next week?
不 得周四见 我周一有其他事
No, actually it's got to be Thursday. I got plans Monday.
有趣的事吗
Something exciting?
女友的父母要来 所以并不是
Girlfriend's folks are in town, so nope.
那就周四吧
Well, uh, Thursday it is.
我喜欢你的画 你画得对
I'm liking yours. That's the way.
用色可真大胆 是不是
You're not shy about using color, are you?
这才像个真正的艺术家
That's the way a real artist…
我要试试这个
I'm gonna try this…
抱歉 宝贝 我…
Sorry, honey. Just, uh…
外公要坐一会儿
Grandpa's gotta sit…
外公
Grandpa?
萨拉
Sara…
天啊
Oh, my God!
好了
OK, very good.
护士没把这个拔掉
The nurse left your thing on.
她可能忘了取下来
Yeah, she probably forgot to take it off.
- 我摘吧 - 我来吧
- I'll get it. - I can get it.
- 你没事吧 - 别烦我了 天啊
- You good? - Quit bugging me. Jeez.
给你
There you go.
屋里好热
It's warm in here.
这用不着
I don't need that.
给我那个
Give me that.
萨拉 只许吃一块曲奇
Sara! One cookie.
对牙齿不好
Bad for your teeth.
谢谢
Thanks.
头发涂什么颜色
What color for the hair?
妈妈
Mom?
想涂什么都行
Whatever you want.
我会选深褐色
But I'd say brunette.
他举双手投降 他放弃了
He's got his arms in the air. He's given up.
他抽出一根棍子
He's got a stick out and…
- 一下下痛打他 - 关掉 崔克 好恶心
- He just, like, pounds on him. - Turn it off, Trick. It's gross.
是什么
What is it?
这下可好 行走的告密机器
Great. The walking snitch.
- 她没告过密 - 她只是奇怪而已
- She never snitches. - She's just weird.
我想知道你们在看什么
I want to know what you're watching.
关你什么事 芯片脑袋
What do you care, chip-head?
视频有脏标 你看不了
It's parental advisory. You're locked out.
我想知道
I want to know.
你还是别看了 我看了都后悔了
You're better off not seeing it. Wish I never did.
要是我告诉你它讲的是什么呢 这样行吗
What if I tell you what's in it? That work?
他打倒了他 砰一下 血溅得到处都是
So, he brings it down, like, wham! There's all this blood.
你见过血吗
You seen much blood?
像果汁一样 粘稠的红色果汁
It's like juice. Thick, red juice.
那个倒在地上的人说「不要」
Then the guy on the ground is all, like, "Hell, no!"
但他继续…
And he keeps…
太过了 把我的脸印在传单上我无所谓
It's too much. I'm fine to have my face on the flier,
但海报感觉像是在说「看我」
but on the poster, it's like, "Look at me."
萨拉 你干什么
Sara, what are you doing?
萨拉
Sara!
这幅图讲的是什么
What's happening in this picture?
他们快乐还是
Are they happy or…
他们在说话
They're talking.
仅仅是说话吗
Just talking?
我不知道说的什么
I don't know what about.
好 下一幅
OK. Next one.
- 这幅呢 - 我不知道
- How about that one? - I don't know.
她快乐吗
Is she happy?
她的病…就像是自闭症
So is this, like, an autism thing?
自闭症多种多样 但我觉得她不是自闭
The spectrum is wide, but in my opinion, she's not on it.
但铅笔呢 她自残
But what about the pencils, like, self-harm?
还有她画的这些画
And these pictures are…
萨拉之前有没有表现出不适当的愤怒
Has Sara ever shown any undue anger before now?
没有
No.
那么可以算是实验
Well, then consider this part experiment,
和发脾气 是做给你看的
part acting out, for your benefit.
方舟天使没能在全国范围内推广
The Arkangel never launched nationwide.
在欧洲遭禁
It was banned in Europe.
到秋天 在这里也会被叫停
It'll be pulled here, too, by the fall.
是我害了她
I did this to her.
你无法移除植入物
You can't remove the implant,
但可以丢掉父母监视器
but you can get rid of the parental unit.
那个屏幕
The screen.
扔掉它 问题就解决了
Just throw it away. Problem solved.
过滤关
Filter off.
再见
Goodbye.
今天就靠你自己了 好吗
You're gonna be on your own today. OK?
没有方舟天使
No Arkangel.
我不打开系统
The system isn't gonna be on.
好吗 眼前不会模糊不清
OK? So, no fuzzy pictures.
你也看不到我
And you won't see me?
我看不到你
I won't see you.
但别害怕 我就在街这边
But, you do not have to be afraid. I'm right down the street.
- 要是出事了 你也不知道 - 不会出事的
- You won't know if something happens? - Nothing is gonna happen.
我们必须这样
It's important that we do this.
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
要乖乖的 宝贝
Be good, sweetie.
小心
Watch out!
小心 孩子
Watch it, kid.
快快快
Come on, come on, come on.
（萨拉距您1.8英里）
好了 够了
OK! OK, this is enough!
别再碰我东西 崔克
Don't touch my stuff again, Trick.
是吗 我想怎样就怎样
Yeah? I'll do what I want.
你想干什么
What do you want?
你没事吧
Are you OK?
没事
Yeah, sure.
等我爸看见 会让我添道伤的
My dad's gonna see this and then bust it all over again,
因为我惹麻烦了
'cause I got in trouble.
之前没见过人嘴唇被打破吗
Ever seen a bust lip before?
现在见到了
Not till now.
她关掉了系统
She turned the system off.
好吧
Ok…
这是黄片 这是人在干
This is porn. Like, people doing it.
这样没法造人
They can't make babies that way.
想造人得换个方法
They have to do it different for that.
他拿了一把锯
So this one's got a hacksaw.
要锯掉自己的脚
and he's gotta cut his own foot off.
这名恐怖分子
So, the terrorist guy…
好 好 盯着那把刀
OK, OK, keep an eye on the knife.
瞧见没
See?
他要把他整个脑袋切下来啦
He's gonna take his whole head off!
要乖乖的 宝贝
Be good, sweetie.
真乖 小皮
Good boy, Petey.
你好好玩吧
You hang on in there.
- 你加东西了 - 是种新的益生素吧
- You added something. - Oh, it's like a new kind of probiotic.
- 能让你大便紧实 - 真恶心 老妈
- It keeps your stools firm. - Oh, Jesus, Mom.
你逗我呢吧
Oh, you've got to be kidding!
你上次出门是多久之前了
When was the last time you went anywhere?
这可不算跳舞
That's not dancing.
她说他是英国人
She said he was English.
他才不是英国人
He's not English.
她说他说话一股外国调调
She said he said "cup of tea, " or something.
这又说明不了什么 苏珊是个傻瓜
Doesn't mean anything. Susan's an idiot.
是崔克
Hey, it's Trick.
我的天 他买车了
Holy fuck, he's got wheels!
崔克
Yo, Trick!
哥几个好啊
Hey, guys. What's up?
- 神发型 - 闭嘴
- Interesting hair. - Shut up.
我逗你呢 挺好看的
I'm fucking with you. It's cool.
- 你还好吗 - 不知道你还在乎我
- How are you doing? - Didn't know you cared.
没准我不在乎呢
Maybe I don't.
- 你开车送货吗 - 差不多
- You a delivery guy now? - Kinda.
- 算是吧 - 闭嘴
- Of sorts. - Shut up.
挺有趣嘛 我得走了
So intriguing. I gotta go.
话说 过一会儿我们要去道斯顿湖
Hey, uh, we're headed to Lake Dalston later.
你们俩想一起去吗
if you girls want to hang.
看看再说吧
We'll think about it.
- 肯定很好玩 - 一起去吧
- It'll be fun. - Why don't you just come?
来嘛
Come on!
我爸才不会让我上崔克的车呢
Like my dad's gonna let me set foot in Trick's van.
这样 我们就跟家长说今晚去莱丽家看电影
Look, we tell our folks we're at Reilly's for movie night.
来吧 肯定能成的
Oh, come on, it'll work.
值得一试吧
It's worth a shot, I guess.
话说啊
So, anyhow…
- 你和崔克是不是那啥呀 - 什么啊
- You and, uh, Trick, huh? - What?
我什么都不会做的
I'm not gonna do anything.
- 是吗 好吧 - 去你的
- Yeah, OK. Sure. - Oh, fuck you!
你回来了
You're home.
不待久 我要和梅丽尔去莱丽家看电影
Not for long. I was gonna go to Reilly's with Meryl. Movie night.
电影之夜不是周三吗
Oh, I thought movie night was on Wednesday.
她妈妈周三晚上有客人 就改到今晚了
Her mom's got guests over then, so we're doing tonight.
打算看些老电影 早餐飞车党什么的
Gonna watch some vintage thing. The Breakfast Gang.
是《早餐俱乐部》
The Breakfast Club.
就是那个
That's it.
大约11：30回家吧 她妈会送我回来的
Um, be home, like, 11:30. Her mom will drop me back.
正好我也要出门 所以
Well, I might be heading out, too. So…
- 真的 - 是啊 真的
- Really? - Yeah, really.
好 谁晚回家谁就是坏蛋
OK. Last one home's a rotten egg.
好吧
Ok!
你好啊 怎么样
Hey, there. How you doing?
你挺辣的 回见
You look hot. Later.
很辣吗
I don't know…
她说我胖 我忍了 但我还记得
She called me fat. I got over it. I still remember it…
- 想来点吗 - 行啊
- Would you like some? - Yeah, sure.
- 那是什么 - 我听见了
- What was that? - I heard it.
冷吗
Cold?
有点吧
Only a bit.
来
Come here.
不早了
It's late.
我该走了
I should go.
下周再见啊
Same time next week?
我是萨拉 请留言 说点好听的
Hi, it's Sara. Leave a message. Make it good.
我是妈妈 给我回电
Hey, it's Mom. All right, call me.
好吗 再见
OK? All right, bye.
艾娃 我就是想问问
Ava. I was just wondering.
孩子们电影看完了没
if the girls were done with the movie.
什么电影
What movie?
- 《早餐俱乐部》 - 她们今晚没来啊
- Breakfast Club? - They never ended up here.
- 没有吗 - 没 要不你问问莱丽
- They didn't? - No. Do you want to speak to Reilly?
我也不知道 我大概是记错了
I don't know. I must have got my wires crossed.
- 多谢了 - 好的
- OK, thanks. - All right.
- 你好 - 我是玛丽
- Hello? - Hi, it's Marie.
我想问问萨拉和梅丽尔在一起吗
I was wondering if Sara and Meryl were together.
她说她们今天要去莱丽家
They said they were headed down to Reilly's.
没有啊 我没看见她们
No, I haven't seen them.
我是萨拉的母亲玛丽
Hi, it's Marie, Sara's mom.
- 我就是想问问 - 什么事
- Yeah, I was just… - What's up?
- 她跟你联系过吗 - 没有
- Have you heard from her? - Uh… no.
抱歉这么晚打搅你 我想问问你见到她了吗
I'm sorry, I know it's late. I was wondering, have you seen her?
- 没有 出什么事了吗 - 没事没事
- No. Everything OK? - No, everything's fine.
我是萨拉 请留言 说点好听的
Hi, it's Sara. Leave a message. Make it good.
我是妈妈 你在哪 快点回电
Um, hey, it's Mom. Where are you? Call me.
我是萨拉 请留言 说点好听的
Hi, it's Sara. Leave a message. Make it good.
萨拉
Sara?
快点快点快点快点快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
快点啊 赶快的 快点快点
Come on, come on! Come on, come on, come on.
（萨拉距您4.3英里）
怎么回事
What is that?
使劲操我
Fuck me harder.
操我
Fuck me.
- 我的天啊 - 求你了
- Oh, God, oh… - Please.
来 我来
Here. Let me do it.
我的手还算暖和
My hands are warm.
- 你肯定是个骗子 - 怎么了
- You gotta be a liar. - What?
你说你从来没做过
You said you'd never done that before.
你才不像是从来没做过的
No way you never done that before.
我对天发誓
Swear to God.
其实 你不用说那种话的
You know, you didn't have to talk like that.
什么话
Like what?
就是黄片里叫床的那种
Like the porn stuff.
你不用为我那么说
I mean, like, you don't have to talk like that… for me.
好吧
Ok.
怎么了
What?
就是 你啊
Just… just you.
我怎么了
What about me?
你知道吗
You know…
你一身腱子肉 不过嘛
You've got muscles, but…
你就是一软蛋
…you're a pussy.
好吧
Yeah.
我被发现了 我妈知道我不在莱丽家
I'm busted. My mom knows I'm not at Reilly's.
真的
Yeah, I mean…
我们得回去了 好吧
We gotta go, OK?
- 快点 - 该死
- Come on. - Fuck.
（萨拉距您2.4英里）
（萨拉距您2.3英里）
没开灯 也许她还没回来
No lights. Maybe she's still out.
我确定她约会去了
Pretty sure she had a date.
也许她也滚床单了呢
Maybe she got laid.
闭嘴吧你 真恶心
Oh, please, that's gross.
- 抱歉 - 瞧你乐的
- Sorry. - Check out that laugh.
- 是吗 - 是啊
- Yeah? - Yeah.
回见
Later.
萨拉
Sara?
- 抱歉 妈妈 我回来晚了 - 没事
- Sorry, Mom. I am a little late. - It's OK.
莱丽怎么样
How was Reilly?
她挺好
She's great.
我去睡觉啦
I gotta go to bed.
- 好的 - 晚安 妈妈
- OK. - Night, Mom.
我爱你
I love you.
又加益生素了
Hmm, probiotics.
我走了
I gotta go.
我今天放学晚回来会儿
I'm gonna be a little late back from school.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
约好了要帮梅丽尔做课业
Said I'd help Meryl with a project.
她还挺认真的 所以
She's being a dork about it, so…
- 那好 - 回见
- OK. - See ya!
再见
Bye!
- 祝您下午愉快 - 谢谢你 亲爱的
- Have a good afternoon. - Thank you, dear.
好 你觉得怎么样
All right. What do you think?
是挺好的 但我不能喷在车上
OK, that's awesome, but I can't put that on the van.
- 为什么 - 首先 那不是我的车
- Why not? - Well, A, it's not my van,
其次 我最好不要太张扬
and, B, it's better if I'm anonymous.
因为你要运特别的货吗
For your special delivery?
也许吧
Maybe, yeah.
- 你身上带了吗 - 带什么了
- You got any on you? - Any what?
得了吧 崔克 我不傻 我知道你卖什么
Oh, come on, Trick. I'm not dumb. I know what you sell.
带了吗
You got any?
不适合你
It's not for you.
肯定在你背包里
Bet it's in your backpack.
- 在座位底下 - 萨拉
- Under the seat… - Sara.
- 和带子放在一起 - 过来
- With tape. - Come here.
- 萨拉 还给我 - 胶带
- Hey, Sara, give me that. - Duct tape.
还给我 不行不行
Give me that. No, no, no.
快点给我
Come on, give me that.
- 肯定在袋子里 - 没有
- I bet it's in the pocket. - No!
我只是挣点小钱好赶紧搬出去 好吗
I'm making a little money on the side so I can move out, OK?
我不吸那东西
It's not like I use that shit.
你试过吗
Have you tried it?
我当然吸过 但那又不是什么好货
Of course I've tried it but, I mean, it's not even good coke,
就一般般
it's, like, average.
是专门给那些
It's for people who like to.
喜欢整天自夸的人的 嘚嘚嘚
talk about themselves all the time. Yada yada yada.
让我看看是什么样子
Show me what it looks like.
拜托 我就想看看
Come on. I just want to see.
求你了
Please.
你确定这不是白糖吗
Are you sure it's not sugar?
得了吧你
Go away.
有一种吸法就是把这东西放在
So, one of the things people do is they put it, like…
- 牙龈下边 下牙龈 - 好吧
- under their gum, bottom gum. - OK.
这样
So…
真恶心
Gross.
好了 先收起来吧
All right, let's, uh, let's put it back.
- 你最好不要 - 我想试试
- I don't think you should… - I want to try some.
就一点 就一次
Just a little, just once.
就一次
Just once.
（心率过高）
（毒品警报）
（雅绅特家具仓库超市）
- 您需要点什么吗 - 我来找人
- Hi, can I help? - I'm just looking.
女士
Ma'am?
你好 你是莱恩·崔贝基吗
Excuse me? Are you Ryan Tribecky?
- 你离我女儿远点 - 我不知道你在说什么
- You stay away from my daughter. - Uh… I don't know what.
萨拉 你知道我在说什么 你离她远点
Sara. You know exactly what I'm talking about. You stay away.
- 那个她 - 她才15岁 你个吸毒的垃圾
- OK, she's… - She is 15, you junkie piece of shit.
你希望我报警吗
You want the cops in on this?
- 我什么都没做 - 我会让警察看你做了什么
- I didn't do anything. - I will show them what you did.
你离她远点 否则我把这个拿给警察看
OK, you stay away from her, or I will show them this. OK?
那个系统你还留着
You still got that system?
没错 所以不管她看见了什么
Yes, I have it. So whatever she sees,
我也能看见 我盯着你呢
I see, and I am watching you.
- 好 - 所以你离她远点
- OK. - So you stay away.
她打给你 你不准接
OK, if she calls you, you hang up.
她来见你 你把她打发走
If she comes to see you, you tell her to get away.
- 你离她远点 - 我会的
- You just stay away from her. - I'll stay away.
你给我离得远远的
You stay the fuck away.
好啊 妈
Hey, Mom.
您试图接入的语音信箱已满
The mailbox you're attempting to reach is full.
请稍后再试
Please try again.
（你在哪）
（你不理我）
（你在哪 你不理我 你什么毛病啊）
（待售）
萨拉
Sara?
晚饭好了
Hey, dinner's ready.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
墨西哥菜哟
It's Mexican.
拜托 我就是
Please, I just…
我困了 我想提前睡 好吗
I'm tired, and I want to sleep, OK?
好
Ok.
（和我说话啊）
所以你要跟我分
So you're cutting me out.
标准的混蛋作风 是这样吗
Standard dick move. That's what this is, right?
看着我
Look at me.
- 你看我一眼怎么了 - 这是个错误
- Why can't you just look at me? - It was a mistake.
我可没觉得是个错误
It didn't seem like a mistake from where I was laying.
我不能和你在一起
I can't be with you.
什么
What the fuck?
我不想和你在一起
I don't want to be with you.
我不喜欢你 明白吗
I don't want you, OK?
我告诉你
You know what?
去你的
Fuck you.
（雷克斯大药房）
好啊 妈
Hey, Mom.
那么他为什么这么难过呢
OK, so why is he so down?
俄狄浦斯说过
Oedipus says things like:
「发生便发生吧 我定要弄清楚」 再比如
"Let the storm burst, my fixed resolve still holds." Or:
「我决不会被证明是另一个人」
"Nothing can make me other than what I am."
他仍然认为自己负有道德责任
He still holds himself morally responsible.
他并不把自身的苦难怪罪在命运上
He doesn't blame fate for what's happened to him.
而道德责任感是自由意志的彰显
Moral responsibility implies the existence of free will,
但归根结底
but actually…
你感觉好些了吧
You feeling any better?
你听好
So, listen…
我做了一些测试 以防是诺如病毒爆发
I had to run some tests, in case we had a noro outbreak here.
亲爱的 你吐是因为避孕药
Honey, it was the EC pill that made you sick.
- 避孕药 - 紧急事后避孕药
- EC? - Emergency contraception.
是为了中止你的妊娠
For terminating your pregnancy.
我…没怀孕啊
There's no… There's no pregnancy.
真的 我没有
Seriously, I'm… I'm not…
我不可能 我没有
I can't… I haven't…
我理解 亲爱的
I understand, sweetheart.
药片会管用的 就是会有呕吐症状
And it will work, in spite of the vomiting.
这你不用担心了
You don't have to worry about that.
你已经不怀孕了
You're not pregnant anymore.
我得记到你的档案里 但我可以不标出来
I gotta put it in your file, but I don't have to flag it.
我希望你知道 我会照顾你
And I want you to know I got your back.
求你了
Please.
萨拉
Sara?
你监视我
You watched me.
不是 我 亲爱的
No, I… honey…
- 亲爱的 - 你看我和他在一起
- Honey… - You watched me with him.
- 我不是有意的 - 给我
- I… No, I didn't mean to. - Give it to me.
给我
Give it…
我是想保护你 我想让你安全
I was trying to protect you. I was trying to keep you safe.
怎么关掉
How do you turn it off?
- 过滤开 - 我做的一切都是为了你
- Filter on. - Everything I've done, I've done for you.
- 亲爱的 我爱你 - 闭嘴
- Honey, I love you… - Shut up!
莎拉
Sara…
闭嘴
Shut up!
萨拉 萨拉
Sara! Sara!
萨拉
Sara…
过滤关 关 关
Filter off, off, off…
关
Off…
萨拉
Sara?
- 我爱你 - 萨拉
- I love you. - Sara!
萨拉
Sara!
不 不
No… No…
萨拉
Sara!